[
  {
    "question": "The process of doing something again and again, usually to improve it.",
    "correct_answer": "Iterations",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Constraint", "Variable", "Calculation"]
  },


{
  "question": "A method of coming up with alternative solutions.",
  "correct_answer": "Brainstorming",
  "incorrect_answers": [ "Iterations", "Variable", "Probability"
  ]
},
{
  "question": "Someone who wants to know how and why things work. They also design and build things.",
  "correct_answer": "engineer",
  "incorrect_answers": ["astronaut", "firefighter", "scientist"]
},
{
  "question": "Engineers are people who design and build things to solve _____",
  "correct_answer": "problems",
  "incorrect_answers": ["riddles", "crosswords", "puzzles"]
},
{
  "question": "This person searches for answers to technological and natural questions to obtain knowledge of why something is the way it is.",
  "correct_answer": "scientist",
  "incorrect_answers": ["physicist", "astronaut", "entrepreneur"]
},
{
  "question": "Once you've figured out what problem you want to tackle, you need to _____",
  "correct_answer": "do your research",
  "incorrect_answers": ["build a prototype", "design your solution", "test your solution"
  ]
},
{
  "question": "The standards that help engineers measure how well their design does its job.",
  "correct_answer": "criteria",
  "incorrect_answers": ["prototype", "engineer", "failing forward"]
},
{
  "question": "When engineers are trying to solve a problem, they follow a series of _____",
  "correct_answer": "steps",
  "incorrect_answers": ["solutions", "problems", "tests"]
},

{
  "question": "The process of taking something apart and analyzing its workings in detail.",
  "correct_answer": "Reverse Engineering",
  "incorrect_answers": ["Graphic Design", "Evaluation", "Process"]
},
{
  "question": "A simple machine that allows you to test your design.",
  "correct_answer": "prototype",
  "incorrect_answers": ["solution", "iterative process", "product"]
},
{
  "question": "A plan produced to show the workings of an object before it is built or made is known as?",
  "correct_answer": "design",
  "incorrect_answers": ["solution", "prototype", "iterative process"]
},  

{
  "question": "A limit imposed on a design solution.",
  "correct_answer": "Constraint",
  "incorrect_answers": [ "Specification", "Risk/Benefit Trade-Off", "Hindrance"
  ]
}
]
